20now.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy | 20 Now

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the http://20now.com and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to 20now  include http://20now.com and 20now and all 20now web properties. The 20now website is an Online Marketing Services site. By using the 20now website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

##  **Collection of your Personal Information**

20now may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase 20now’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. While we collect this information, we don’t store it directly on our servers, it’s stored on a PCI level-1 merchant system. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. 20now may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age, gender, and various other demographics provided by you. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by 20now. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the 20now website.

20now encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from 20now so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. 20now is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the 20now website.

##  **Use of your Personal Information**

20now collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

20now may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from 20now and its affiliates. 20now may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

20now does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

20now may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to 20now, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

20now will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on 20now or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of 20now; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of 20now, or the public.

##  **Use of Cookies**

The 20now website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize 20now pages, or register with 20now site or services, a cookie helps 20now to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same 20now website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the 20now features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the 20now services or websites you visit.

##  **Security of your Personal Information**

To secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, 20now uses the following:

GeoTrust

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

20now has gone through Extended Validation (EV), a verification process that ensures the 20now parent company, CSR Technologies .com, Inc., is in good standing with the KY Secretary of State, operates a valid Demand-Deposit-Account with a US bank, and is 3rd-party verified as a public business. This Extended Validation is to show you the commitment to your privacy and the integrity of 20now in handling your information.

GeoTrust is an independent, third-party company engaged in the development of digital trust. Verisign provides authentication of Internet services, digital identity and intellectual property. By clicking on the Verisign logo, the Verisign website will serve up a web page that confirms that 20now is “Verisign Authenticated.”

##  **Children Under Thirteen**

20now does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

##  **Disconnecting your 20now  Account from Third Party Websites**

You will be able to connect your 20now account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR 20now ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users can login to facebook and through their privacy settings disable the appropriate app (dependent on the website they are connecting through), which fully disconnects facebook connectivity to that website..

##  **Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from 20now by contacting us via the methods listed below:

##  **Changes to this Statement**

20now will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. 20now encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how 20now is protecting your information.

##  **Contact Information**

20now welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that 20now has not adhered to this Statement, please contact 20now at:

20now, c/o CSR Technologies .com, Inc  
440 Millwood Court  
Bowling Green, Kentucky 42104

Email Address:  
support@20now.com

Telephone number:  
(720) 722-0669

Effective as of March 13, 2013
